// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
      question: "It means when people or a community cannot support their basic needs",
      answer: "Poverty",
      options: [
        "Hunger",
        "Poverty",
        "Sickness",
        "Discrimination",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
      question: "It mirrors individual life in the society; its values, practices, traditions, issues or problems",
      answer: "Literature",
      options: [
        "Literature",
        "Social issues",
        "Change",
        "Society",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
      question: "It is a long-term change in weather due to natural, geological and man-made actions",
      answer: "Climate change",
      options: [
        "Change",
        "Monsoon",
        "Climate change",
        "Climate",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
      question: "It is when the state fails to do its obligation to respect, protect and fulfill the rights",
      answer: "Violation of Human Rights",
      options: [
        "Rules",
        "Social injustice",
        "Rights",
        "Violation of Human Rights",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
      question: "It is a prejudicial action toward a group of people, race or gender",
      answer: "Discrimination",
      options: [
        "Oppresion",
        "Bullying",
        "Social injustice",
        "Discrimination",
    ]
  },{
    numb: 6,
      question: "It is a something unjustice actions are done in society",
      answer: "Social injustice",
      options: [
        "Oppresion",
        "Bullying",
        "Social injustice",
        "Discrimination",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
      question: "Bullying",
      answer: "",
      options: [
          "Oppresion",
          "Bullying",
          "Social injustice",
          "Discrimination",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
      question: "It is an act of subjecting to cruel restraints",
      answer: "Oppresion",
      options: [
          "Oppresion",
          "Bullying",
          "Social injustice",
          "Discrimination",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
      question: "Repetition of same initial consonant sounds in successive or closely associated syllables within a group of words",
      answer: "Alliteration",
      options: [
        "Personification",
        "Hyperbole",
        "Consonace",
        "Alliteration",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
      question: "Repetition of consonant sounds within sentences",
      answer: "Consonace",
      options: [
        "Personification",
        "Hyperbole",
        "Consonace",
        "Alliteration",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
      question: "Exaggerated statements not meant to be taken literally",
      answer: "Hyperbole",
      options: [
        "Personification",
        "Hyperbole",
        "Consonace",
        "Alliteration",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
      question: "Human characteristics are attributed to nonhuman things",
      answer: "Personification",
      options: [
        "Personification",
        "Hyperbole",
        "Consonace",
        "Alliteration",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
      question: "The use of symbols to signify ideas by giving symbolic meanings different from literal meanings",
      answer: "Symbolism",
      options: [
        "Hyperbole",
        "Aliiteration",
        "Symbolism",
        "Consonace",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
      question: "Do everything fast, the time is running",
      answer: "Personification",
      options: [
        "Personification",
        "Hyperbole",
        "Consonace",
        "Alliteration",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
      question: "I've told you a thousand times to read the instructions before responding, but you still don't understand what to do.",
      answer: "Hyperbole",
      options: [
        "Personification",
        "Hyperbole",
        "Consonace",
        "Alliteration",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
      question: "Peter Piper picked a peck of pickled peppers",
      answer: "Alliteration",
      options: [
        "Personification",
        "Hyperbole",
        "Consonace",
        "Alliteration",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
      question: "We shouldn't break the glass since the cracks won't go away no matter how well you construct it",
      answer: "Symbolism",
      options: [
        "Hyperbole",
        "Aliiteration",
        "Symbolism",
        "Consonace",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 18,
      question: "Men cannot be mistreated in the same way as women, who are compelled to dance like puppets",
      answer: "Discrimination",
      options: [
        "Discrimination",
        "Bullying",
        "Justice",
        "Opinion",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
      question: "A few of Ben's classmates tease him for being unable to read and for damaging his belongings",
      answer: "Bullying",
      options: [
        "Discrimination",
        "Bullying",
        "Justice",
        "Opinion",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 20,
      question: "Jane is the top student in her class, but she decided to work rather than go to college since she didnâ€™t have the money for it",
      answer: "Poverty",
      options: [
        "Poverty",
        "Bullying",
        "Discrimination",
        "Money",
    ]
  },


  // you can make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];